A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, RG 2 FA433
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messieurs Rockefeller (OMR) Files, 1878-1972; bulk; 2; 21 Cubic Feet
  - Personal Papers, 1910-1962; 2; 13 box(es)
    - Invitations, 1951-1960 (Box 11, Folder 154 A)
    - Jury Duty, 1942-1959 (Box 12, Folder 155)
      LSR foreman of Special Grand Jury to investigate waterfront crime, 1953-1954.
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1952-1961 (Box 12, Folder 156)
      Character and employment references by LSR
    - Medical, 1942, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Naval Service, 1942-1949, 1955, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 158)
      LSR served February 13, 1942 - November 3, 1945, retiring with rank of Lt. Commander.
    - Office Furnishings, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 159)
      New Furniture, Inc., Arundel Clarke Limited, Inc., J.H. Thorp and Company, Inc.
    - Paintings and Works of Art - General, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 160)
      Victor Joseph Gatto, Edith Halpert, Paul Maze, Mexican Art Exhibition, Bonnard.
    - Paintings and Works of Art - General, 1954-1961; Still Images: 1 black-and-white 7.25" x 9.75" print; and 3 black-and-white 5" x 7" prints. (Box 12, Folder 161)
      Carol Uht inventory of LSR collection; requests for loans for exhibitions. Includes Callery, Toulouse-Lautrec forgery, Renoir, Leger, Rivera, Gainsborough, Bonnard, Karfiol, Cezanne, Zorach, Edith Halpert, Homer. File also includes correspondence from Florence Van Kirk, 1947-1954, concerning Audubon painting of "Osprey and the Otter and the Salmon," and enclosing copies of old photographs of JDR Sr. and his siblings and of buildings in Moravia and Germantown, NY.
    - Paintings and Works of Art - Farré, Henry, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 162)
      LSR purchase of paintings of military aviation scenes for donation to the Air Force Academy.
    - Paintings and Works of Art - Farré, Henry, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 163)
      LSR purchase of paintings of military aviation scenes for donation to the Air Force Academy
    - Paintings and Works of Art - Loans, 1944-1958 (Box 12, Folder 164)
      Bonnard, Dunoyer de Segonzac, Zorach, Cezanne, Homer
    - Photographs, 1948-1960 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      Portrait photographs by Lester K. Henderson, Gabor Eder, Arthur Daley, Frederick Eberstat. No photographs in file.
    - Pocantico Hills House - General, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 166)
      Design, furnishings, landscaping
    - Pocantico Hills House - General, 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Pocantico Hills House - General, 1947-1961 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Alterations, 1950-1952, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 169, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - General, 1936-1938 (Box 13, Folder 170)
      Arcy Corporation (B.J. McGarry, president) insolvency and creditor claims. JDR, Jr. authorizes payment of all outstanding claims against Arcy for LSR's house, July 1937.
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - Payments, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 171)
      Payments to subcontractors and creditors on Arcy Corporation's behalf for work done on Pocantico Hills house or against Cleveland Arcy houses.
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - Payments, 1937 January - June (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - Payments, 1937 July (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - Payments, 1937 August - October (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Arcy Corporation - Payments, 1937 November - 1939 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Bills Paid - Schmidt, Elena B., 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 176)
      Decorator
    - Pocantico Hills House - Bills Paid - Other, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 177)
      Furnishings and fixtures
    - Pocantico Hills House - Estate Services, 1941, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Estimates and Orders, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 179)
      Furnishings
    - Pocantico Hills House - Expense Statements, 1936-1938 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Gardens, 1936-1955 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 13, Folder 181)
      Includes 2 drawings and survey. Correspondents include Alfred Geiffert, Jr., Zenon Schreiber, Mott B. Schmidt
    - Pocantico Hills House - Guest House, 1939-1947 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Pocantico Hills House - Swimming Pool, 1945-1949 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 13, Folder 183)
      Survey, contract, cost statements; issues concerning legality. Includes garden costs.
    - Pocantico Hills House - Underground Lines, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 184)
      Power lines buried along Bedford Road.
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (Lists), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (A-C), 1948; Still Image: black-and-white 3.25" x 4" matte print. (Box 14, Folder 186)
      Includes photograph of painting by Grosvenor Atterbury of his home, "'The Lodge' on Shinnecock Hills," October 1946, enclosed in Grosvenor and Astelle Atterbury to LSR, April 29, 1948.
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (D-G), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (H-L), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (M-O), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (P-S), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Condolences (T-Z), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Memorial Service, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 192)
      Riverside Church, May 23, 1948. 2 booklets retained in file.
    - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - Memorial Window, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 193)
      Union Church of Pocantico hills, booklet and dedication service brochure, May 13, 1956. 3 booklets retained in file
    - Rockefeller, John D. - Condolences, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 194)
    - Rockefeller, John D. - Estate, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 195)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (A-B), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 196)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (C-D), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 197)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (E-G), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (H-I), 1960 (Box 15, Drawer 199)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (J-L), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (M), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (N-R), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (S), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences (T-Z), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences - Lists, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Condolences - Reply forms, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Institutional Condolences and Tributes, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Memorial Resolutions and Editorials, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 208)
      May 15, 1960. 4 copies of memorial booklet retained in file
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Memorial Service, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 209)
      May 15, 1960. Four copies of memorial booklet retained in file.
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Rockefeller Center Memorial, 1960-1961; Still Images: 4 color 8" x 10" prints. (Box 16, Folder 210, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
      Plaque (including photos of the artist's rendering of the "I Believe" plaque at Rockefeller Center), memorial tribute, and historical account of JDR Jr. and founding of Rockefeller Center. Includes correspondence with Joy Buba.
    - Rockwood Hall Property, 1941, 1946-1953 (Box 16, Folder 211)
      Property given to LSR as gift, January 1946
    - Rockwood Hall Property, 1954-1961 (Box 16, Folder 212)
      Property given to LSR as gift, January 1946.
    - Saranac Lake Camps - General, 1945-1953 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      Camp Canaras and Camp Nepawhin
    - Saranac Lake Camps - Gift to Memorial Hospital, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 214)
      Camp Canaras and Camp Nepawhin given to Memorial Hospital for use by the staff
    - Saranac Lake Camps - Gift to Memorial Hospital, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 214 A)
    - Saranac Lake Camps - Purchase, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Schools - College - General, 1927-1932 (Box 16, Folder 216)
      Princeton University
    - Schools - College - General, 1932-1935 (Box 16, Folder 217)
      Harvard Law School
    - Schools - College - Senior Thesis, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 218)
      Princeton University Senior thesis on "The Concept of Value and Its Relation to Ethics"
    - Schools - College - Senior Thesis (Notes), 1929-1932 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Schools - Lincoln School, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - Trips - General, 1935-1955 (Box 17, Drawer 221)
    - Trips - General, 1956-1961 (Box 17, Folder 222)
      Includes itinerary and talking points for 1957 meetings at Pentagon concerning Vertol.
    - Trips - General, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 222 A)
    - Trips - Europe, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 223)
      June - August. Traveled with Vietor Davis.
    - Trips - Europe, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 224)
      June - August. With NAR and Mary Clark Rockefeller.
    - Trips - Europe, 1936-1938, bulk 1937 (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Trips - Jamaica, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Trips - Belgian Congo, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 227)
      Opening of Filtisaf plant.
    - Trips - Europe, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 228)
      Correspondence with Paul Maze.
    - Trips - Africa, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Trips - Venezuela, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    - Trips - Alaska, 1960 February - July; Still Images: 2 black-and-white prints (3" x 5" and 8" x 10"). (Box 17, Drawer 231)
    - Trips - Alaska, 1960 August - 1962; Still Images: 9 black-and-white 3" x 5" glossy photographs, glued to brochure cover and typescript pages. (Box 17, Folder 232)
      LSR toured Alaska with his family from June 19 - July 12, in connection with his work as chair of the Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission. Folder contains follow-up correspondence with Governor William A. Eagan and others; typescript brochure (with photographs)on the Tongass Lodge, Excursion Inlet; and correspondence concerning tourism and investment proposals.
    - Trips - Alaska (Oversized file), 1960 (Box 53, Folder 706)
      Invitation to Tongass Lodge brochure, 1960
    - Trips - Passports, 1927, 1937-1949 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Vermont, 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 234)
      Property purchases and offers. Mount Tom and Suicide Six purchases; Woodstock Community Swimming Pool.
    - Wedding - General, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Wedding - Gifts, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 236)
      Gifts of stock from JDR, Sr. and JDR, Jr.
    - Will, 1951, 1954, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 237)
      Memoranda from John Lockwood concerning trusts and executors.
    - Fishers Island; Pocantico Hills House; Saranac Lake Camps (Oversized file), 1940-1952 (Box 53, Folder 705)
      Map of Fishers Island, 1952; blueprint of service stair, Pocantico Hills House, 1940; proposed garden designs, Pocantico Hills; statement of expenditures on Saranac Lake real estate, 1947
  - Business Interests, 1946-1967; bulk; 3; 9 box(es)
    Files documenting LSR's involvement with specific businesses are generally found in the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, especially in the Business Interests series C available here:
    FA312 Office of the Messrs.Rockefeller records, Business Interests, Series C
    The Business Interests series concerns primarily LSR's resort developments in the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico. The series contains a few files relating to LSR's sponsorship of television and film productions, a dossier on negotiations with Howard Hughes in 1954 to purchase the Hughes Tool Company and Aircraft division, and a file containing various proposals for business ventures, but the rest of the series pertains to LSR's involvement in resort development and his creation of the Virgin Islands National Park.
    The variety of files in this series seems to reflect differences in provenance. General geographic files (e.g., Hawaii, Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands, St. John) contain miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda on local issues, assorted development proposals, property negotiations, and resort-related issues. Files for Dorado, Puerto Rico and for the Dorado Beach Estates and Hotel concern LSR's negotiations with the property owner Clara Livingston and with Puerto Rican authorities concerning development plans, property purchase, financing, design, and construction of the resort. Files for St. John and the correspondence files (under Virgin Islands) for Frank Stick detail the local intelligence, public relations, and patchwork assembling of property that permitted the creation of the Virgin Islands National Park.
    Public relations files concerning the opening of the Caneel Bay resort and the National Park dedication (December 1, 1956) and the opening of the Dorado Beach Hotel two years later (December 1, 1958) form the largest part of the Business Interests series. In both cases, the opening public relations files concern planning and arrangements for the opening celebrations. Files include multiple drafts of guest lists, letters of invitation, schedules and opening plans, speeches, press releases, and correspondence on transportation and publicity arrangements. The Caneel Bay resort opening coincided with the dedication ceremonies for the Virgin Islands National Park and the public celebration planned for the occasion. An invitational golf tournament capped the inaugural celebrations for the Dorado Beach Hotel resort.
    While LSR pioneered the field of venture capital, there is little in this series that addresses these aspects of his Business Interests. There are a few files in the Personal Papers series that concern LSR's Brokerage Business on the New York Stock Exchange. In the same series Aviation Interests files contain reports and memoranda relating to LSR's business interests in aviation. There are also scattered discussions of business investments and opportunities contained within LSR's Correspondence files.
    Significant correspondents include Allston Boyer, Robert L. Hoke, Frank Stick, Gerald R. Flamm, Conrad Wirth, Wallace Harrison, Theodore Moscoso, Eddie Rickenbacker, Robert Moses, Luis Munoz Marin, Ward Canaday, Joe Jennen, Leslie Moore.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1955-1956 May (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 June-September (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 October (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 November 1-15; Still Images: 4 black-and-white 8" x 10" prints. (Box 18, Folder 241)
      Includes photos of LSR and family at a ceremony relating to the Virgin Islands National Park, NOvember 10, 1956. NPS photos by Abbie Rowe; enclosed in Conrad Wirth to LSR, November 15, 1956. Photos marked 3900 A-D.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 November 16-22 (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 November 23-30 (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - General, 1956 December - 1957 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Acknowledgements - Boyer, Allston, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 245)
      Brief thank-you letters.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Acknowledgements - Hoke, Robert L., 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Acknowledgements - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1956-1957 (I) (Box 18, Folder 247)
      From LSR, arranged chronologically.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Acknowledgements - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1956-1957 (II) (Box 18, Folder 248)
      To LSR, arranged alphabetically by name or by affiliation.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Board of Directors, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 249)
      Includes agenda for December 2 meeting.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Drafts of Letters, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 250)
      Dated and undated drafts concerning planning and arrangments
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Guest List, 1956 (Box 18, Drawer 251)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Special Guests (A-Z), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 252)
      Letters of invitation and responses, filed alphabetically
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Invitations - United States Press, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 254)
      Press and tourism officials. Includes letter from Lawrence McEvitt, on St. Thomas attitudes toward Caneel Bay and Park development.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - National Park Service Press Releases, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Planning and Operations, [1956] (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Planning and Operations, 1956 October-November (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Planning and Operations, 1956 November-December (Box 19, Folder 258)
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Souvenir Letters, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 259)
      Cover letters for photographs of opening ceremonies and boards.
    - Caneel Bay Opening Public Relations - Speech, 1956 December 1 (Box 19, Folder 260)
      LSR speech at Dedication of Virgin Islands National Park (draft by Arthur Tourtellot). Includes version by Gerald Flamm for Spanish translation, with reference to Puerto Rico. Duplicates removed.
    - Caribbean Islands - General, 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 261)
      Caribbean Tourist Association meeting; Pigeon Island; Green turtle project.
    - Caribbean Islands - Appeals, 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 262)
      Appeals from various schools and organizations; most declined.
    - Caribbean Islands - Contributions - General, 1956-1961 (Box 19, Folder 263)
    - Caribbean Islands - Contributions - Boys' Town (Dorado, Puerto Rico), 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 264)
      Child Welfare League survey and proposed relocation of the institution.
    - Caribbean Islands - Contributions - Boys' Town (Dorado, Puerto Rico), 1958 January (Box 19, Folder 265)
      Report of a Survey of the Society for the Protection and Defense of Children (Boys Town), Dorado, Puerto Rico, January 1958. Child Welfare League of America, Inc.
    - Caribbean Islands - Contributions - Boys' Town (Dorado, Puerto Rico), 1958 April - 1961 (Box 20, Folder 266)
      Spanish translation of Boys' Town report. LSR offer to purchase the Pueblo del Nino and gifts of securities.
    - Cornwall Productions - General, 1953-1957 (Box 20, Folder 267)
      Syndicated television program, "Janet Dean Registered Nurse," featuring Ella Raines Olds.
    - Cornwall Productions - Agreement, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 268)
      William Dozier, Ella Raines Olds, Colonel Robin Olds, Edgar Peterson
    - Cornwall Productions - Certificate of Incorporation, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 269)
    - Cornwall Productions - Financing, 1952-1957 (Box 20, Folder 270)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - General, 1952-1956 (Box 20, Folder 271)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - General, 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 272)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - General, 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 272 A)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Financing (Puerto Rico Industrial Development Company), 1953-1954 March (Box 20, Folder 273)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Financing (Puerto Rico Industrial Development Company), 1954 May-1959 (Box 20, Folder 274)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Golf Club - General, 1955, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 275)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Golf Club - Berwind Golf Club, 1953-1955 (Box 20, Folder 276)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Golf Club - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 277)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Livingston Property Negotiations for Purchase, 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 278)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Livingston Property Negotiations for Purchase, 1955-1957 (Box 20, Folder 279)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Municipal Beach - Appraisal, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 280)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Municipal Beach - Deed, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 281)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Municipal Beach - Meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 282)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Municipal Beach - Preliminaries to Land Gift, 1955-1961 (Box 21, Folder 283, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
    - Dorado Beach Estates, Inc., 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - General, 1953-1957 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 21, Folder 285)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - General, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 286)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Letters of Appreciation, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening - General, 1958-1959, 1969, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - General, 1957-1958 August (Box 21, Folder 290)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - General, 1958 September-October (Box 21, Folder 291)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - General, 1958 November (Box 21, Folder 292)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - General, 1958 December-1959 (Box 21, Folder 293)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Congratulatory Messages, 1958 November-December (Box 21, Folder 294)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Dinner, 1958 December 1 (Box 21, Folder 295)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Film Proposals, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 296)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Invitational Tournament, 1957 September-1958 May (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Invitational Tournament, 1958 July-September; Still Images: 12 black-and-white 8" x 10" prints (2 sets of 6 images). (Box 22, Folder 298)
      Includes publicity photos of professional golfers Ed (Porky) Oliver, Julius Boros, Don Finsterwald, Dick Mayer, Gene Sarazen, and Claude Harmon.
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Invitational Tournament, 1958 October-December (Box 22, Folder 299)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Invitational Tournament, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 300)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Pre-Opening Luncheons and Receptions, 1958 January-April (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Pre-Opening Luncheons and Receptions, 1958 May (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Golf Club - Pre-Opening Press Luncheon (New York), 1958 April-May (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - General, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Lists (I), 1958 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Lists (II) (Press and Tournament), 1958 (Box 23, Folder 306)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Press Acknowledgements, 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 307)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Special Guests Acknowledgements, 1958 October (Box 23, Folder 308)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Special Guests Acknowledgements, 1958 November-December (Box 23, Folder 309)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Invitations - Special Guests Regrets, 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 310)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Opening Public Relations - Organization (I), [1957-1958] (Box 23, Folder 311)